Okay, as you can see, I'm totally out of position for pose fifteen.
So I'm going to take you back to thirteen and get you back into the pose so we can add a hand to this.
I'm going to point my left toe straight ahead with a straight leg and get my right leg positioned in a ninety degree angle.
The right heel is just to the back of the right, the left heel so that it creates this ninety degree angle.
The right toe is pointed straight out to the side.
In pose fourteen, we added one hand.
In pose fifteen, we're going to add two hands.
So bring both hands up to the hip.
Again, keep your focus into camera and notice that the body is totally broad to narrow by adding two elbows up.
And I have a wide view of the clothing that I'm wearing, particularly pants.
Pants are really fun to model because the longer the leg and, most print models have nice long legs, you really get to show off the pant leg.
We want to show the flare, if it's narrow at the bottom or flared at the bottom.
We also want to show any designs that are on the pant.
So in pose fifteen, you can show the sleeves and the pants particularly well with a very broad pose.